

[Muhamad Aldi Setiawan]

Sepatan Timur, Kabuptaen Tangerang Indonesia, 15520 | +62 895334930931 | muhamadaldisetiawan00@gmail.com

About me

I am a web developer focused on creating responsive and user-friendly applications or systems. With experience as a Front End and Full Stack web developer, I have succeeded in creating various interesting web applications. My skills include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, php and databases as well as frameworks such as React (including Vite and Js) to provide a great user experience. Apart from that, I also have experience in back-end development using Laravel, and Express

Abilities & Competencies

Hard Skills:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- React JS
- PHP
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- Laravel
- ExpressJs
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Postgre

Soft Skills:

- Honest and Responsible
- Open-mindedness
- Time Management
- Creativity
- Problem Solving
- Learn Independently
- Able To Work Tndividually and In a Team

Education

Muhammadiyah University of Tangerang (2018-2022)

S1 Teknik Informatika - IPK 3,50

Work experience

1. PT.TELKOM INDONESIA

Web Application

July 2023 - Now

 My duties include analyzing user needs, developing internal applications such as monitoring dashboards, and integrating between databases to ensure efficient and connected data flow.

2. PT APPINESTOPIA

Full Stack Developer

January 2022- July 2023

• I am responsible for creating the Kementrian Lingkungan Hidup dan Kehutanan (KLHK) website and applications using the React.js and Laravel frameworks, including designing the database, as well as building the necessary business logic and functionality.

3. CV SAMUDERA BIRU NUSANTARA

Web Developer

January 2021- January 2022

• My duties include designing, developing, and managing company profile websites to present corporate identity online, creating internal applications to support internal company operations such as human resource management or inventory management, and managing the company's server infrastructure to ensure availability, security, and optimal performance.